<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mfunds</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fund">FundActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="FundsSummary">

    "A fundamental idea in finance is the relationship between risk and return. The greater the    "
    "amount of risk an investor is willing to take, the greater the potential return. Investors    "
    "need to be compensated for taking on additional risk. For example, a U.S. Treasury bond is    "
    "bond, provides a lower rate of return. A corporation is much more likely to go bankrupt than  "
    "the U.S. government. Because the risk of investing in a corporate bond is higher, investors   "
    "are offered a higher rate of return.\n\n Low Risk\n                                                        "

    "                                                                                              "

    "A portfolio contain holdings of solely bonds, cash, cash equivelants and money market can be  "
    "considered as low risk as generally the economy has little impact on the return of the bond.  "
    "The disadvantage of a portfolio of bonds is that the return can be consideraly less but its a "
    "safe option. Generally in the last phases of a pension plan as it matures it will solely      "
    "contain funds with low risk and the inception of a pension plan will contain high risk funds. "
    "The risk will generally decrease throughout each phase of the pension plan.\n\n Medium Risk\n "

    "Fund managers tend to mix bonds with equity to lower risk of the portfolio, generally called a"
    "balanced fund. The bonds within the portfolio can be considered as safety net when there is a "
    "down turn in the economy. A portfolio with a balance of equity and bonds can limit the damage "
    "to an investors return.\n\n  High Risk\n                                                      "

    "Funds containing holdings purely of equity stock are considered high risk however they can    "
    "have the highest of returns but they are very exposed to economic downturn. Fund managers have"
    "a variety of styles on how to manage portfolios. Basically they actively managed the fund by  "
    "adding or removing stocks. Some fund managers tend to track an index to keep the fund inline  "
    "with the economy while others will try to outperform the enconomy and increase an investors   "
    "return. This can be viewed as aggressive management however additional costs will be incured  "
    "incured on the investor.\n\n Note\n                                                           "
    "                                                                                              "
    "                                                                                              "
    "There are many different types of portofolios with various options (blends e.g.), styles of   "
    "investment and risk algorithms. The above explains a very basic perspective of mutual funds   "
    "while there many complex strategies/views.\n\n Compare Funds Investment Growth\n              "
    "                                                                                              "
    "Investors require some sort of barometer to gauge the performance of their funds with their   "
    "investment or investments over time. A typical technique is to use the growth of 10,000. This "
    "is demonstrated by a graph that shows an initial investment of 10000. The chart is used to    "
    "typically compare the returns from various investments against each other or another benchmark"
    "e.g. SP 500 over a period of time. The disadvantage about this chart is that it excludes     "
    "fund management fees and other charges such as sales and redemption expenses, the growth shown"
    "is overstated, and the actual returns that would accrue to an investor would be lower than    "
    "those shown.\n\n
    "The next page provides you with 2 questions, the level of risk that you are comfortable with  "
    "and how much you want to invest. Based on your criteria a list of funds will be recommended.  "
    "By selecting a fund from the list you will be presented with information containing details on"
    "the fund of interest.                                                                         "






    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_funds">FundsActivity</string>
    <string name="inceptiondate">Inception Date</string>
    <string name="ytdreturn">YTD Return</string>
    <string name="navps">Nav PS</string>
    <string name="change">Change</string>
    <string name="mer">MER</string>
    <string name="assets">Assets($mil)</string>
    <string name="rank">Rank(1Yr)</string>
    <string name="stddev">StdDev(3Yr)</string>
    <string name="volatilerank">VolatilityRanking(3Yr)</string>
    <string name="rrsp">RRSP Eligibility</string>
    <string name="load">Load </string>
    <string name="maxfrontend">Max Front End</string>
    <string name="maxbackend">Max Back End</string>
    <string name="saleopen">Sale Open</string>
    <string name="morningstarrisk">Morning Star Risk</string>
    <string name="morningstarrate">Morning Star Rating</string>
    <string name="netasset">Net Asset Value</string>
    <string name="fullname">Full Name</string>
    <string name="fundfees">Fees</string>
    <string name="manager">Manager</string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Mutual Funds</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test">TestActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>

</resources>
